https://www.ukparks.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyBy using the UK Parks website, you accept the terms of our Privacy Policy.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our websites and not to information collected offline.
BH&HPA’s Privacy Notice explaining how the Association processes data is on this link. Please contact enquiries@bhhpa.org.uk if you have any concerns.
Measuring website usage using Google Analytics cookies
We use Google Analytics to find out how people interact with our site.
Google Analytics stores information about what pages you have visited, how you arrived there and how long you spend on the site. Google Analytics does not collect or store any personal information used to identify who you are such as your name or address. We do not allow Google to use or share our analytics data. For more information about Google Analytics cookies go to Google Privacy Policy.
Links to external sites from our websites
The websites contain links to other third party websites. These websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy and UK Parks / BH&HPA is not responsible for the privacy practices within any of these other websites. You should be aware of this when you leave the websites and we encourage you to read the privacy statements of other websites.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
If this Privacy Policy changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this webpage. If you do not agree with the changes we make please do not continue to use the websites. Regularly reviewing this webpage ensures you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties.
Terms & Conditions
Please visit our Terms & Conditions page for information about use, disclaimers and limitations of liability governing the use of our websites.
Copyright BH & HPA
